Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series XI. Schools and Divisions, 1977-1991; 153318; 20.43 Linear Feet in 49 manuscript boxes.
  - Planning Reports from Various NYU School and Divisions, 1985-1987 (Box 227, Folder 8-9)
  - Division of Libraries Five Year Plan 1987-1992, 1986 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Five Year Plans for Various NYU Schools and Divisions, 1986-1987 (Box 228, Folder 2-4)
  - Analysis of Federal FY1988 Budget Proposals and Impact on NYU, circa 1986-1986 (Box 228, Folder 5-6)
  - Greek Culture Center, 1981-1982 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - La Pietra Clipping, 1983 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Background, 1982-1983 (Box 229, Folder 3-4)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Greek Trip Background Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 229, Folder 5-6)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Preliminary Material, 1982 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Proposal, January 1983 Version (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Briefing Book, Greece, 1983-01-08-1983-01-10 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) Program -- Daily Briefing Book, Greece, 1983-01-08-1983-01-10 (Box 180, Folder 2-3)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Greek Trip, 1983-01-08-1983-01-10 (Box 180, Folder 4-5)
  - Greek Cultural Center -- Proposed Informational Materials, circa 1982-1983 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program -- Greek Trip Follow-up, January 1983 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Planning Meeting, 1983-01-13 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Greece Trip, January 1983 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Greek-American Press Briefing, 1983-02-09 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Greek Trip Follow-Up, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Thank You Letters re: Greece Trip, February 1983 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Coordination Correspondence RESTRICTED, February -- March 1983 (Box 140, Folder 3-4)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Briefing Book and Working Book, June 1983 (Box 181, Folder 4-5)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA), 1983 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Papandreou Letter -- Original RESTRICTED, 1983 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Gerassimos Arsenis -- Background RESTRICTED, 1983 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Brochure and Application Form Planning, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Brochure and Application Form Planning, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Certificates, circa 1983 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - NYU Bulletin, 1985-1968 -- Edited (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Planning Commission Study Group, 1985 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Five Year Planning Report -- Arts and Science, February 1987 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Six Year Report, 1987 (Box 182, Folder 5-7)
  - Long-Range Plan -- Interim Report of the University-wide Planning Commission -- Summary Reports, October 1988 (Box 182, Folder 8-9)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Resource Network Summer Events, 1990 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - NYU Yeronisos Island Excavation and Training Program, 1990 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Spanish House at NYU Concept, 1990 (Box 222, Folder 8)
- Series XII. Student Affairs, 1971-1991; 153188; 6.70 Linear Feet in 16 manuscript boxes.
  This series contains subjects relating to NYU students, including financial aid; housing; South African students at NYU; fraternities; sports teams; and student groups, such as the Gay Students Union. Files date from 1971 to 1991 and typically contain correspondence, reports, magazine articles, and press clippings. There are a significant number of files in this series containing admissions statistical reports and admission intervention request-related correspondence.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in chronological order.
  - Admissions RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Financial Aid RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 194, Folder 7, Box 196, Folder 1-3)
  - Reports, 1988 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Student Loan Issues RESTRICTED, 1980-1982; 153317 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Report of the NYU Intercollegiate Athletics Advisory Committee, 1971-1982; 153316 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Gay Students' Union, 1981-1982; 153315 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Student Housing Issues RESTRICTED, 1980-1982; 153314 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Student Aid RESTRICTED, 1981-1982; 153313 (Box 212, Folder 3-4)
  - Scholarships and Awards RESTRICTED, 1980-1982; 153311 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Publications -- Newspapers, 1981; 153310 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Student Groups, 1981-1982; 153309 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Financial Aid RESTRICTED, 1982-1984; 153308 (Box 212, Folder 6-7)
  - Financial Aid -- Loans, 1982; 153306 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Financial Aid -- Scholarships and Grants RESTRICTED, 1982-1983; 153305 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - South Africa Education Program, 1980-1981; 153304 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Integration of Business Schools, circa 1982; 153303 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - Placement Services, 1982; 153302 (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Student Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1982-1985; 153301 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Tzong-Huey Lin RESTRICTED, 1980-1981; 153300 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - United Negro College Fund (UNCF) Study of Black Students, 1981; 153299 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Application Process Issues RESTRICTED, 1981-1982; 153298 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Application Statistics Reports, 1981-1982; 153297 (Box 211, Folder 11-12)
  - Admissions: Interventions RESTRICTED, 1981-1983; 153296 (Box 213, Folder 4-7)
  - Graduate Student Orientation, 1984; 153294 (Box 211, Folder 13)
  - Office of the Registrar Enrollment Reports, 1983-1985; 153293 (Box 211, Folder 14-15)
  - Admissions Interventions RESTRICTED, 1984; 153289 (Box 213, Folder 8, Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Admissions Statistical Reports, 1984-1985; 153287 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Classification, 1984; 153286 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - Fencing Championship, 1984; 153285 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Political Science Graduate Student Association, 1985; 153284 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - FIJI (Phi Gamma Delta) Fraternity, 1985, 1987; 153283 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Student Senate, 1984; 153282 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Student Senator Council, 1985; 153280 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - Student Health Services, 1984-1985; 153279 (Box 215, Folder 8)
  - Student Housing Issues RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Financial Aid RESTRICTED, 1984-1985; 153278 (Box 214, Folder 3-4)
  - Scholarships RESTRICTED, 1984-1985; 153277 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - South African Education Program, 1984-1988; 153276 (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - Project Opportunity, 1984-1985; 153275 (Box 215, Folder 10)
  - Admission Intervention RESTRICTED, 1984-1985; 153274 (Box 214, Folder 6-7)
  - Condolence Letters RESTRICTED, 1985; 153270 (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - Admission Intervention RESTRICTED, 1985-1986; 153269 (Box 214, Folder 9, Box 216, Folder 1-2, Box 217)
  - Correspondence re: Student and Staff Issues RESTRICTED, 1983-1985; 153268 (Box 216, Folder 3-5)
  - Sports, 1987; 153266 (Box 215, Folder 11)
  - Students Requests for Acceptance RESTRICTED, 1986; 153265 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Student Deposit Statistics, 1987; 153263 (Box 215, Folder 12)
  - Reports, 1986; 153262 (Box 215, Folder 13)
  - Admission Requests RESTRICTED, 1987; 153261 (Box 217, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence re: Student Issues RESTRICTED, 1986-1987; 153260 (Box 218, Folder 1-5)
  - Sports and Recreation Development, 1986; 153257 (Box 215, Folder 14)
  - Gay and Lesbian Union, 1986-1987; 153255 (Box 215, Folder 15)
  - Collegiate Association for the Research of Principles (CARP) Convention, 1986; 153254 (Box 215, Folder 16)
  - Psi Upsilon Building, 1985-1986; 153252 (Box 215, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1987; 153251 (Box 215, Folder 18)
  - Report of Drug Use Survey, 1986; 153250 (Box 215, Folder 19)
  - Student Residence Issues RESTRICTED, 1986, 1988; 153248 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Student Issues RESTRICTED, 1986-1988; 153247 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Internal Communications, 1987; 153244 (Box 215, Folder 20)
  - Awards and Internships, 1986; 153240 (Box 215, Folder 21)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions Yearbook, 1987, 1989; 153239 (Box 215, Folder 22)
  - Student Publications, 1986; 153238 (Box 215, Folder 23)
  - Reports of Registration, 1986; 153237 (Box 215, Folder 24)
  - Student Issues RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1991; 153232 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Internal Communications, 1988, 1990; 153231 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - FY 1988 Annual Survey of Students Charges and Financial Aid Grants, 153230 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Executive Development Committee Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989; 153223 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Resource Network: Report on Activities, 1989-1990; 153222 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1988; 153221 (Box 219, Folder 5-7)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1990-1991; 153220 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Cambridge Associates Report on Student Charges, 1990; 153219 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Gazette Article, 1989; 153218 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Student Enrollment Reports, 1989; 153216 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Sports and Recreation, 1989-1990; 153215 (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1989; 153213 (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - AAUS Conference, 1990; 153212 (Box 220, Folder 10)
  - Student Housing Issues RESTRICTED, 1989-1991; 153211 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Student Financial Aid Issues RESTRICTED, 1990; 153210 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Social Sciences Research Council's International Predissertation Fellowship Program Issue, 1990-1991; 153209 (Box 220, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships RESTRICTED, 1989; 153208 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - South African Program, 1989-1990; 153200 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - First Cross-School Schedule of Classes, Fall, 1989; 153196 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - College of Arts and Science Year Book Presidential Letter, 1991; 153195 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Student Issues RESTRICTED, 1991; 153193 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1990; 153192 (Box 221, Folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1989-1990; 153191 (Box 223, Folder 1-4)
  - Data on Student Aid, 1982 (Box 241, Folder 3-4)
  - The Changing Demand for Educational Skills, 1982 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Gambling with Our Future -- Final Staff Draft, 1983 (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - South African Schools and Students -- NYU, 1987-1988 (Box 241, Folder 7)
  - Women in Education, 1984 (Box 241, Folder 8)
- Series XIII. Speeches and Writings, 1981-1991; 54394; 22.50 Linear Feet in 54 manuscript boxes.; 1 audiocassette; 3 videocassettes (vhs)
  This series contains John Bradmas' speeches, writings, and interviews while serving as President of NYU. The speeches (1981 to 1991) are from events including NYU graduations, Board of Trustee and Senate University meetings, and other public appearances. Speech files often contain final copy and drafts; notes; and informational memos containing event location, time/date, and background. Three of these speech files also include video recordings. Unless otherwise stated, the speeches were delivered by Brademas. Yearly NYU graduation ceremony files often contain detailed schedules, event programs, and speeches from all presenters. This series also contains op-ed pieces, articles, and memos written by Brademas. Presidential greetings and letters for use by various NYU publications are also in this series.
  - Budget Cut Discussion, Congressional Breakfast (Washington, D.C.), 1981-04-08; 55823 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - NYU Oxford-Cambridge Boat Race Dinner, Harvard Club (New York, NY), 1981-04-15; 176984 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Investiture of Honorable Ray Thorton, President of Arkansas State University (Jonesboro, AR), 1981-04-16; 55822 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Address Re: International Education, Springfield College (Springfield, MA), 1981-05-24; 55821 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - NYU Law School Convocation, 1981-05-28; 55820 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - Testimonial by Laurence Tisch at Dinner for Brademas, Corcoran Gallery (Washington, D.C.), 1981-06-08; 55818 (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - "The Christian Faith and the Public Order," Commencement Address, McCormick Theological Seminary (Chicago, IL), 1981-06-09; 176985 (Box 242, Folder 7)
  - Welcome Message for Summer Orientation in The New Torch, 1981-06-11; 55815 (Box 242, Folder 8)
  - "The Role of the Federal Government in Support of Museums," Conference on Italian and American Museums (Milan, Italy), 1981-06-24; 55814 (Box 242, Folder 9)
  - Career in Business Reception, Graduate School of Business Administration (NYU), 1981-07-09; 55810 (Box 242, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration Arts Institute (NYU), 1981-07-17; 55813 (Box 242, Folder 11)
  - Address Re: International Education, Foreign Lawyers Workshop Dinner (NYU), 1981-07-23; 55812 (Box 242, Folder 12)
  - Anglo-American Conference on University Admininistration, Rockefeller Plaza (New York, NY), 1981-07-28; 55811 (Box 242, Folder 13)
  - Chios Arts and Museums, Ionic Center Seminar (Chios, Greece), August 1981; 55807 (Box 242, Folder 14)
  - "American Higher Education and The Federal Role" (Chios, Greece), August 1981; 55804 (Box 242, Folder 15)
  - "The Role of Congress in American Foreign Policy" (Chios, Greece), August 1981; 55806 (Box 242, Folder 16)
  - Speech Re: International Education (Chios, Greece), 1981-08-10; 55805 (Box 242, Folder 17)
  - "Greek American Involvement in Contempory American Politics" (Chios, Greece), August 1981; 55808 (Box 242, Folder 18)
  - Quarterly Management Committee Meeting for ARA Services (NYU), 1981-08-12; 55809 (Box 242, Folder 19)
  - Writers at Work Program (NYU), 1981-09-18; 55803 (Box 242, Folder 20)
  - Freshman Orientation (NYU), 1981-09-21; 55802 (Box 242, Folder 21)
  - Address Honoring George P. Livanos by the American Parkinson Disease Association, Waldorf Astoria Hotel (New York, NY), 1981-09-22; 55800 (Box 242, Folder 22)
  - Presidential Citation to Czeslaw Milosz (NYU), 1981-09-22; 55801 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - "The Architecture of NYU", 1981-09-23; 55798 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Remarks by Herbert Silverman on "The Architecture of NYU" (NYU), 1981-09-23; 55797 (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Luncheon for Cardinal Franz König (NYU), 1981-09-28; 55796 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Presentation of the Delmore Schwartz Prize to Constance Urdang (NYU), 1981-09-30; 55794 (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Introduction to Bernard Crick Seminar on "British-Irish Relations" (NYU), 1981-10-01; 55793 (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - Community Leaders Reception (NYU), 1981-10-05; 176988 (Box 243, Folder 7)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Fund Workers Committee Meeting, 1981-10-06; 176989 (Box 243, Folder 8)
  - Inaugural Remarks, 1981-10-09; 55792 (Box 243, Folder 9)
  - Trustee Presentation (NYU), 1981-10-12 (Box 243, Folder 10)
  - Proclamation of NYU Week at City Hall (New York, NY), 1981-10-13; 55789 (Box 243, Folder 11)
  - Remarks by Herbert Silverman Re: Proclamation of NYU Week at City Hall (New York, NY), 1981-10-13; 55788 (Box 243, Folder 12)
  - Remarks by Laurence Tisch Re: Proclamation of NYU Week at City Hall, 1981-10-13; 55787 (Box 243, Folder 13)
  - Inaugural Medal of Freedom Award Dinner for Theodore Hesburgh, 1981-10-13; 55790 (Box 243, Folder 14)
  - NYU Inauguration of John Brademas -- Inaugural Brunch at Avery Fisher Hall (New York, NY), 1981-10-14; 55782 (Box 243, Folder 15)
  - NYU Inauguration of John Brademas -- Program, Tickets, Press Release, Avery Fischer Hall (New York, NY), 1981-10-14; 55786 (Box 243, Folder 16)
  - NYU Inauguration of John Brademas -- Press Release, 1981-10-14; 176991 (Box 243, Folder 17)
  - NYU Inauguration of John Brademas -- Remarks by L. Jay Oliva for Inaugural Ceremonies, 1981-10-14; 176992 (Box 243, Folder 18)
  - NYU Inauguration of John Brademas -- Remarks by Herbert Silverman, Avery Fisher Hall (New York, NY), 1981-10-14; 55783 (Box 243, Folder 19)
  - NYU Inauguration of John Brademas -- Remarks by Laurence Tisch, Avery Fisher Hall (New York, NY), 1981-10-14; 55785 (Box 243, Folder 20)
  - NYU Inauguration of John Brademas -- Remarks by Michael Widman, Avery Fisher Hall (New York, NY), 1981-10-14; 55781 (Box 243, Folder 21)
  - NYU Inauguration of John Brademas -- Address, Press Kit, Avery Fisher Hall (New York, NY), 1981-10-14; 55775 (Box 243, Folder 22)
  - NYU Inauguration of John Brademas -- Inaugural Dinner, 1981-10-14; 55780 (Box 243, Folder 23)
  - NYU Inauguration of John Brademas -- Remarks by Laurence Tisch at Inaugural Dinner, 1981-10-14; 55784 (Box 243, Folder 24)
  - Presidential Foreword to Sequicentennial Calendar, October 1981; 55779 (Box 243, Folder 25)
  - Lecture Re: NYU and the Arts at the Faculty of Arts and Science "Dimensions of Change" Conference (NYU), 1981-10-15; 55774 (Box 243, Folder 26)
  - Introduction of Professor James Tobin (NYU), 1981-10-16; 176999 (Box 243, Folder 27)
  - Town Hall Friend of the Arts Award (The New York University Club, New York), 1981-10-18; 55773 (Box 243, Folder 27)
  - NYU Annual Report -- Drafts, 1981-10-19; 55772 (Box 243, Folder 28)
  - Dedication of the Coles Sports and Recreation Center (NYU), 1981-10-24; 55770 (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - Remarks by Laurence Tisch, Dedication of the Coles Center (NYU), 1981-10-24; 55769 (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - Remarks Re: Goals for NYU, Gallatin Dinner (NYU), 1981-10-26; 55771 (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Award Presented to Dr. Jerome S. Coles, Varsity Club Dinner (NYU), 1981-10-27; 55768 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Breakfast for Dr. Hans-Jochen Vogel (Deutsches Haus, NYU), 1981-10-28; 55767 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Degree Presentation to Professor Kurt Otto Friedrichs (Courant Institute for Mathematical Sciences, NYU), 1981-10-30; 55766 (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - State of the University Address to the Board of Trustees (NYU), 1981-11-02 (Box 244, Box 7-8)
  - State of the University Address to the Board of Trustees (NYU), 1981-11-02 (Box 244, Box 9-10)
  - Remarks Re: International Studies, Institute of Fine Arts (NYU), 1981-11-04; 55763 (Box 244, Folder 11)
  - Remarks Re: Federal Funds for Education, Public Education Association Luncheon (Waldorf-Astoria, NY), 1981-11-04; 55764 (Box 244, Folder 12)
  - Dental Alumni Day (NYU), 1981-11-06; 177013 (Box 244, Folder 13)
  - Remarks Re: Government Funds for Libraries, New York Library Association Conference (Statler Hilton Hotel, NY), 1981-11-07; 55762 (Box 244, Folder 14)
  - "The Academy and the Main Human Enterprise," Miller Committee Lecture Series (Urbana-Champaign, IL), 1981-11-09; 55761 (Box 244, Folder 15)
  - Liberal Arts Education and Study in Spain Colloquium (NYU), 1981-11-13; 55760 (Box 244, Folder 16)
  - Remarks Re: the Liberal Arts, Vanderbilt Associates Dinner (NYU), 1981-11-18; 55758 (Box 244, Folder 17)
  - Remarks Re: International Education for the U.S. and Greece, Hellenic Chamber of Commerce, 1981-11-19; 55757 (Box 244, Folder 18)
  - Remarks Re: NYU Goals, Association for a Better New York Breakfast (Waldorf-Astoria, NY), 1981-11-20; 55756 (Box 244, Folder 19)
  - "Higher Learning and the Nation's Future," Carnegie Foundation Colloquium (Georgetown University, Washington, D.C.), 1981-11-24; 55755 (Box 244, Folder 20)
  - Remarks Re: Fundraising Goals, Division of Student Affairs and Services (NYU), 1981-11-24; 55754 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Remarks Re: Development, Corporate Dinner, 1981-11-24; 55753 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Remarks Re: NYU and Science, American Physical Society (NYU), 1981-12-03; 55752 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Henry Draper Symposium (NYU), 1981-12-04; 55751 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Letter to Board of Trustees, 1981-12-08 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration Faculty Meeting, 1981-12-08 (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Remarks Re: Problems in Higher Education, the Higher Education Group (Washington, D.C.), 1981-12-08; 55747 (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - Remarks Re: Congress and Foreign Policy, Council on Foreign Affairs Dinner (Washington, D.C.), 1981-12-09; 55748 (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - State of the University Presentation to the University Senate (NYU), 1981-12-10; 55746 (Box 245, Folder 9-10)
  - Remarks Re: the Liberal Arts, the Research Libraries Group (NYU), 1981-12-10; 55745 (Box 245, Folder 11)
  - School of Continuing Education Faculty Meeting (NYU), 1981-12-11; 55743 (Box 245, Folder 12)
  - Taft Accolades for Walter Mondale (Plaza Hotel, NY), 1981-12-10; 55744 (Box 245, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Meeting of Arts and Science (NYU), 1981-12-14; 55742 (Box 245, Folder 14)
  - Remarks Re: the Liberal Arts, the Academic Libraries Frontier (UCLA), 1981-12-16; 55741 (Box 245, Folder 15)
  - Presentation of Sesquicentennial Crystal to Bayrd Still, 1981-12-18; 177015 (Box 245, Folder 16)
  - Institute of Afro-American Affairs Reception, 1981-12-21; 177014 (Box 245, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Meeting of the School of Education, Nursing, Health, and the Arts Professions (SEHNAP) (NYU), 1981-12-21; 177016 (Box 245, Folder 18)
  - Statement for the NYU Annual Report for 1980-1981, 55759 (Box 245, Folder 19)
  - Comments on Ancillary Services Project Capital Improvements, 1982; 177017 (Box 245, Folder 20)
  - Report to the Faculty of School of the Arts (NYU), 1982-01-05; 55740 (Box 245, Folder 21)
  - Remarks Re: International Education, Fulbright Commission in Israel (Jerusalem, Israel), 1982-01-12; 55739 (Box 245, Folder 22)
  - Remarks Re: NYU Programs in Television and Communications (NYU), 1982-01-28; 55738 (Box 245, Folder 23)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1982-02-03; 55736 (Box 245, Folder 24)
  - Greenwich Village Chamber of Commerce Luncheon (NYU), 1982-02-03; 55737 (Box 245, Folder 25)
  - School of Social Work Report to the Faculty (NYU), 1982-02-08; 55735 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Remarks by George Heyman to the Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees (NYU), 1982-02-08 (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees Meeting, 1982-02-08 (Box 257, Folder 3)
  - Faculty of Business Administration (NYU), 1982-02-09; 55732 (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - Report to the University Senate (NYU), 1982-02-11; 55731 (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - Ribbon Cutting of Brittany Residence Hall (NYU), 1982-02-12; 55730 (Box 257, Folder 6)
  - Deloitte Haskins and Sells Reception (New York University Club, NY), 1982-02-18; 55728 (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - Remarks by Ruth Farkas, Laurence Tisch, Herbert Silverman, and John Brademas, Palm Beach Dinner (Palm Beach, FL), 1982-02-18; 55729 (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - Report to Dental Faculty (NYU), 1982-03-01; 55727 (Box 257, Folder 9)
  - Remarks Re: International Education, United Nations Foreign Language Week (UN Headquarters, NY), 1982-03-01; 55726 (Box 257, Folder 10)
  - Remarks Re: the Effect of Budget Cuts on Education, Rockefeller Center Luncheon Club (New York, NY), 1982-03-02; 55725 (Box 257, Folder 11)
  - Reception and Presentation of Gift from the Education and Vocation for the Deaf Foundation (NYU), 1982-03-02; 55724 (Box 257, Folder 12)